I created a zero brownie brand called
Charlie Brownie Junior lots of interested people
but i feel like we're making this stop
then everything wrong
we go on this
move away from 1 New Guy look here o
hand cap
then it's over bro Charlie Brown here bison fourteen
what do you think about seven boxes
a ten fits
the same time
effort that we are going after fish
small we could
use for
whale fishing
is on
I think it's that way
we try to find a way for Charlie Brown eh
we go on this
get some brownies to take bro
not much catches some no no no
take box not five
boot in pocket to get to
coming now so you have to get to the caruda
saw it and then how are you doing brother ok
we are from a brand called Charlie Brown
Junior you see the car there is all screwed on
I would like to understand how you can
see a possibility
to put the brownies here on the shelves
to be able to sell
who negotiates this part of
so the manager has already left in charge
that girl over there the manager
already gone out part is with Marco
thank you
hole is lower
ah it took a while
I tried to keep myself away but you
the guy the guy already knows about the product
it's already connected whatever it is
Santos also has a network here from Santos
it's belonging nor bro
but we are looking
some supermarkets that make senses of us
see how we do it to have a moment
what do you think there do you think it gives fit
guy can I get your Zap clear
and this is the product that we have already been trying so hard
the process
fabril nutritional table back here
a hug brother tamo together valeu
but that's it for hunting
whale is that way not an easy sale
but it takes a certain shot
we hit it we can scale it more there
fair time ne
there is a food fair that will roll
in São Paulo bora